PSB heard over
I hate you, I hate you, yes!
I hate you, yes!
He really is amazing!
Well, I suppose they're not too bad.
Those girls, they haven't studied this song yet in their lessons. When did they learn it?
Those girls just won't give up.
This is a closed rehearsal. What are you girls doing?
Please let us observe your lesson, please!
Yeah, we won't get in your way, we promise!
Please!
They were still persistent. I let them stay at the edge of the lesson room.
They were really excited about it.
Ready and...
Let's go! AKP 0048!
AKP 0048!
Let's go!
øre
つなみに
We'll be right back soon.
...
Tomo-Chin, we're leaving you behind.
Wait!
Good work, everyone!
I was so nervous up there.
My knees were shaking!
You were both really fantastic!
You were so cool!
Yeah, you were!
That's my sister!
Mm-hmm.
Chieri, you were amazing, too!
Really?
Memori-san, you were overflowing with pheromones!
Oh, really?
Do you think so?
You did great, Megu.
Ugh.
Oh, Megu?
What are you doing?
I found a video of the members participating in the peace ceremony on the news.
What?
Let's see!
What is that?
World of Justice 0048 gave the citizens courage with their beautiful voices.
Oh!
Oh, man.
It disappeared.
DES interference.
But Takamina-san was so cool.
Kanata, you're a total Takamina-san supporter.
It's not like that, really.
Kanata-san.
What?
Takamina-san and the others should be coming home now.
Huh?
Oh, no!
Sister.
She sure loves Takamina-san, doesn't she?
Yeah.
Let's go welcome them home, too.
Yeah, I guess so.
Takamina-san!
Huh?
Good work today!
Thanks.
I hope you put on a good performance in our absence.
Did you?
Yeah!
Now you've said it.
I'll check the video later to see how you did.
Ow.
You guys didn't like it, guys!
Let's get this meeting started.
The planet of our next concert, Tundra Star,
is under the effect of a total entertainment ban.
The fans there demand an appearance from us,
but we cannot avoid conflict with the DES.
It will be an unpredictable guerrilla concert.
Guerrilla concert?
A planet with a total entertainment ban?
Conflict is unavoidable.
Consequently, we will be taking special measures for this concert.
Kanata.
Yes!
Memori.
Megumi.
Yes!
And finally, all the 77th Generation trainees.
You'll be understudies.
You want understudies to perform at a guerrilla concert?
Amazing.
I can't believe we'll have the chance to appear on stage!
Hold on a minute.
Why the 77th Generation?
Why am I the only one from the 76th Generation?
Can the 76th Generation sing and dance all the songs on today's set list?
Well, answer me.
Despite not being selected as members,
the entire 77th Generation continued to practice.
What was the 76th Generation doing during that time?
I told you before,
the only thing to do is practice.
That's all.
Takamina-san!
Huh?
Do you have a minute?
It's Kanata.
I'm so glad I caught you.
You can count on me being your understudy.
I'll do my very best.
You don't need to worry about a thing.
I won't let you down.
Yeah, thanks.
You just keep practicing.
Yeah!
Kanata!
Huh?
Everyone's already heading towards the station!
Okay!
Well, good luck on your next job then.
Takamina.
Huh?
Do you think I did something wrong?
How do you think the original Takamina-san
would have reacted in that kind of situation?
I'm sure that
she would have smiled and motivated her junior.
I don't really understand anymore.
I couldn't make a very Takamina-like expression.
I don't know what's come over me.
I don't know what's going over me.
This is so frustrating!
Please don't cry, Hazuki.
But we became trainees way before them!
It's just not fair!
Come on, calm down.
Kanata-san.
Please, there's no need to get so worked up.
Girls who work hard will get their turn eventually.
Let's grab the next chance when it comes.
You've got a point.
Next time.
Is that really what you believe?
What about you, Kanata-senpai?
What do you believe?
Your opportunity has never come,
but you still keep working hard as a trainee.
If it were me,
I'd be too ashamed to continue in Zero Zero.
What did you say?
Sonata, it's okay.
That's unforgivable!
Starting to date, I'll call you nasty!
Take this!
Sonata!
Sonata, I headbutted you.
If I headbutt you, it hurts me just as much.
So I won't apologize.
But Megumi-san,
I demand that you apologize to Kanata-san!
Megu, let's go!
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Megumi-san has a head like a rock.
You've got a bomb!
Pain, pain, go away to Megumi!
Suzuko, thanks.
Kanata-san.
But it's okay.
I actually understand how they feel.
We were pretty upset too, you know?
Yeah.
Kanata's right.
When Yoko, I mean, when Sei became a successor before us, we panicked.
It was terrible.
Sai-san was part of the 76th generation?
That's right.
But she's so nice.
She felt sorry for us.
She was so apologetic.
All of us felt really bad about it.
Yeah.
Come on.
Chef Papa's dinner is waiting for us.
Let's go back to the dorm.
Okay!
I'm really sorry for your soul and the idea of a house.
Oh, that's great.
An understudy at a concert.
I wonder if someone like me can do it.
You shouldn't sell yourself short.
Huh?
If you don't perform with confidence,
it's rude to the girls who weren't chosen to be on stage.
I've always thought you were kind of nice, T-Eddie.
That's really good advice, you know?
What?
You're right.
I'll try to be confident.
Hey, when you get nervous, do your molars ever itch?
Hmm?
Ah, right here!
See?
What was that for, T-Eddie?
I thought you might be able to fit an entire orange in your huge mouth.
Oh, that's impossible.
Oh, cheery.
How are you doing?
I will be performing in a concert as an understudy soon.
I'm moving closer to my dream of becoming one of the idols that you hate, but...
But someday, Mamoru, I hope you'll come see me perform on stage.
So, uh...
You guys shouldn't snoop like that.
It's not nice.
It's a letter.
And it's addressed to a boy.
First, we'll enter the target sector with Kaiusha and get a read on the situation.
Then, we'll descend a Tundra Star in the Flying Ghet.
Let us go to meet our adoring fans.
We haven't slept in these beds for a while, huh?
Hey, I look forward to working with you, Megumi-san.
So, shall we go practice?
What?
But I thought we just finished practicing!
No excuses.
Katsuyusha's got a lesson room we can use now.
Let's get to work, guys!
Wow, Kaneda-san's sure fired up, isn't she?
Haha, I'm sure she doesn't want to let down her beloved Takamina-san!
Did you say something?
Hehehehe!
Oh!
Oh, come on and practice with us.
No thanks.
I'll pass.
Megumi…
Bye-bye, Nasty!
I love you, I am in love with you, I will run with all the strength I have.
Why are you practicing with Kaneda-san and the others?
Yoko.
It's Se now.
I'm not Yoko anymore.
You'll always be Yoko!
What's wrong, Megu?
You're acting really strange.
You think I'm acting strange?
There's no way you could understand me anymore, Yoko!
Uh…
You left everyone else in the 76th generation behind and became a successor.
We used to be together all the time, but now we're always apart.
Megu…
I'm sorry.
What are you apologizing for?
Uh…
I guess you're right.
It'd be better if you didn't try to associate with trainees.
Seisan.
Megu…
Whoa!
That's crazy!
Rene, aren't you on a diet?
Thanks to our hard lessons, I lost a little weight, so I quit.
Whoa!
That's a ton of food!
Um…
Girls, do you have a minute?
We got in touch with the WOTA members already on site.
WOTA?
They're the people who helped us at the Handshake event.
According to their report, the DES is calling in reinforcements from nearby planets.
We believe the DGTO intends to use this concert as an opportunity to capture all of Zero Zero.
But that's…
We just don't have enough combat members or LAS to handle them.
For the sake of your safety, the concert is cancelled.
Let's do it!
Takamina.
But you'd be putting yourselves in danger.
A little danger's got nothing to do with it.
We put our lives on the line to sing and dance for the people waiting for us.
Isn't that what AKB0048 does?
I'll do it!
I'd follow Takamina-san anywhere!
You too?
Kanada?
Kanada is the one who should be Takamina.
If I graduate, she can become a successor.
But…
A DES attack?
Already?
Looks like they're here to greet us.
All hands!
Battle stations!
Roger that!
What should we do?
Change into combat uniforms!
Stand by!
Let's go!
Got it!
Four enemy units.
Takamina!
Sayaka!
Sai!
Yes!
Draw the enemy units as far away from the planet as you can.
We'll move cutting you to the safety in the meantime.
Here we go!
Okay!
Let's go!
Wan's music!
He goes!
Let's go!
Shiny Engine!
Two adults!
Go!
Let's go!
First off!
It's a fake sure damn thing!
Whatever.
Go!
other members. Takamina, look. They're attacking our ship. The sub engines. This isn't good.
Tsubasa-san, I'm going too. Takamina's acting strange today. Okay. Are there any other members
who can pilot an LAS? Let me go and do it. Karada. My father taught me to pilot a base
type of the LAS. I may not be the best, but I'm what you've got, so let me do it. But
you're still a... Please let me. Very well. I'm going then. Block 7, emergency lockdown.
Takamina! Are you all right? Two new units incoming.
Be careful, girl. Takamina, this isn't working. What should we do? Takamina?
Sayaka, watch out!
What? How did she... Takamina! Takamina!
Takamina! Takamina's pod has been recovered. Requesting retrieval. Roger. We'll send a recovery
shuttle for her. Wait, Kanita! The enemy units are manned.
You gotta be kidding me! You think you can take more of the things I love from me? You
will?
Okay.
Don't worry!
Let's go with me.
Takamina's pod has been recovered.
Requesting retrieval.
Roger. We'll send a recovery shuttle for her.
Wait, Kanata!
The enemy units are manned!
You've gotta be kidding me!
You think you can take more of the things I love from me?
You bastard!
The Kiras...
They're illuminating Kanata.
They're showing Kanata is the true Minami Takahashi.
Takamina-san!
No.
That isn't my name.
Takamina-san! Takamina-san!
Takamina-san!
You're finally awake. You must have made up for all the sleep you lost from your hard schedule. She was worried about you because you wouldn't wake up. She said she wanted to stay until you regained consciousness, but she must be tired from her first mission. I forced her to leave.
I couldn't protect Takamira-san.
You weren't acting like yourself today. What happened to calmly, carefully, correctly? That's your motto, right?
I don't want to quit yet. Huh? I'm not good at singing. I'm not that great at dancing either. I had no confidence because I was nothing.
But when I was chosen to be the fifth generation Takamina, I finally felt confident in myself.
I want to stay, Takamina. I want to stay a part of Zero Zero. I don't want to graduate.
But as long as I stay, Kanara will remain trainee forever. She works so hard. She looks up to me so much with those shining, honest eyes. She...
But I... But I... But I'm being selfish. And stealing her dream from her for the sake of my own.
What's wrong with that? What?
You may care for all those girls. But the most important thing is the dream you have. Your own dream.
My own dream? My own dream? What do you mean?
We're all chasing the same dream as members of Zero Zero. But each of our dreams are slightly different.
Sharing your dream with someone else is just a fantasy. Your dream is yours and yours alone. What's wrong with that?
More. More. More. And more. I have to gain more strength. I have to put in more effort. I have to do more. Much more.
Much more.